likestool.com 2016-11-05

# Privacy Policy

## Personal information

1\. All the information that Likestool.com gather from the users are private and secured. Likestool.com only collect personal information from you when you provide it to Likestool.com, such as when you: (1) register; (2) place an order to use Likestool.com services; (3) participate in one of Likestool.com promotions; (4) or (5) contact to Likestool.com. The personal information that Likestool.com collect from you may include your name, e-mail address. Data regarding your visit(s) to Likestool.com and any use of Likestool.com resources are collected, which includes location data, weblogs, traffic data, and any other communication information. 

## Use of your information

2\. Your information gives Likestool.com an opportunity to create and offer services for you. Here are the list of how Likestool.com use your data. 

a. Your information will not be sold or used on any other site but Likestool.com. 

b. When you make any request to Likestool.com you let Likestool.com use your information provided Likestool.com with, regarding to the Likestool.com products or services. If you give a permission to Likestool.com may also send information on products or services you may be interested in. 

c. We may use data or let third parties use information that is not related to goods or services you may be interested in. This can be done only in the case of your permission.If you don't want to give consent for our site or third party you can use the opportunity to decline. If you decline once we will remove your details from any third party communications or mailings. 

d. All your data that we have will be stored on secure servers. Transaction data is encrypted for your safety. Note: data via online transmission is not entirely secure. We cannot warrant total protection and security data, we only take all reasonable action to protect information sent to us online. Transmission of any data by you is at your own risk. You take the responsibility for the passwords safety and confidentiality. 

## Links to third party webpages

3\. Likestool.com contains links to other sites, which may have privacy policies that differ from Likestool.com own. Likestool.com are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites. Likestool.com does not endorse any linked websites, or the information, materials, products or services that are contained in or accessible through such linked websites. You acknowledge and agree that Likestool.com is not responsible for the content, accuracy, legality, decency, copyright compliance, privacy practices, security or any other aspects of any such linked websites, and that the access or use of any such linked websites is solely at your own risk, and you hereby waive any and all claims against Likestool.com with respect to such linked websites. 

## Use of cookies

4\. In some cases Likestool.com use cookies to collect mathematical information regarding to Likestool.com services and advertisers. There is no personal information share that could identify you. Any information that collected is for statistical use only about Likestool.com visitors and how they have used Likestool.com services. Likestool.com may collect information about your common internet use with a cookie file. The required information by the cookie helps Likestool.com to improve the website and services suggested to you. You have an opportunity to decline cookies by setting your browser options to decline all cookies. Remember: if you decline the download of cookies some features of Likestool.com may not work. 

## Information exposure

5\. Likestool.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people without your permission except under the following conditions. 

  * Likestool.com respond to legal processes, subpoenas, court orders, or to establish or exercise Likestool.com legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * In case of selling any or all of Likestool.com business to a third party your information may be shared.

## Children's privacy

6\. Any child should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to Likestool.com, or anyone online for that matter. Likestool.com is not intended for anyone under the age of 18 with the exception of those who are 14 years of age or older and have obtained permission from their parent or legal guardian. Refund and Cancellation Policy 

7\. Likestool.com always does the best to build the communication between Likestool.com and it's users in trust and be highly reliable. Likestool.com has a fair refund and cancellation policy. Cancellations will be considered only if the request is made within 24 hours of placing an order. Likestool.com does not accept cancellation requests for items(coins) that you are already used. When you purchase Likestool.com services, your purchase is covered by our 1-day money-back guarantee. There might be cases that you are not entirely happy with your purchase and/or haven't used all purchased coins, in such cases we will cheerfully issue a full refund. In order to request a refund, you should simply contact us with your purchase details within one (1) day of your purchase. Please include your order number (sent to you via email after ordering) and optionally tell us why you’re requesting a refund. The customeres feedbacks are very important for Likestool.com and are used to progressively improve the quality of services. Refunds can not be provided for services that you have aready used, as Likestool.com add coins to your account balance immediately after purchase is done. Refunds are being processed within 7 days after refund order accepted. 

## Contacting Likestool.com

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at: support@Likestool.com
